First Last

SaaS Sales Manager

Sales Manager with 12 years of experience in high-profile SaaS sales and utilizing the innovative online sales channels. Specializes in customer recurrence through direct cooperation with the marketing teams on remarketing programs. Led skill-optimized teams of 5-25 team members.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Resume Worded, New York, NY

SaaS Sales Manager 05/2020 - Present

- Aided the team in reaching 27% sales increase in market launch period of a new service branch, through the management of the new service by creating a valuation model with the customisation of settings and the inclusion of competitive influence
- Preserved the client database and devised personalized customer outreach initiatives to generate recurring business, increasing the subscription renewal rate by 20% in 2021
- Led the sales team to explore the prospect of subscription sales in competition's SaaS client bases, resulting in the takeover of over 20% clients of the major domestic competitor.
- Spearheaded the growth in company revenue by 10% in the first 6 months of work

Growthsi, San Francisco, CA

Sales Manager 02/2018 – 04/2020

- Introduced a new key account customer strategy within the department, causing a 20% growth of customer retention statistic
- Managed 3 distinctive and successful remarketing campaigns,
 achieving about 120% predicted sales goal achievement on average
- Devised a set of experience-based guides to carry out new sales personnel training, improving the average employee efficiency in the first 3 months by 20%

Prepared and led a staff of 25 salespeople, achieving a record 15% growth in company revenue in 2019
 Resume Worded's Exciting Company, New York, NY
 SaaS Territory Sales Executive 03/2010 – 01/2018

- Doubled the annual revenue based on online sales in target groups
 between 2014 and 2016
- Pinpointed and closed the sale on 3 largest customer accounts that were responsible for 15% of yearly revenue in 2017
- Constructed a team of 10 experienced sales specialists, accounting for the 30% increase in niche market share in the territory
- Consistently achieved a 125% of the quarterly target over the course of 2012-2015
- Closely cooperated with the Marketing team, resulting in 40% increase of brand recognition in strategic market groups
- Spearheaded the introduction of an innovative service model dedicated for elderly business owners, resulting in 30% of market share in the said segment

CONTACT

- Denver, OH (Open to Remote)
- +1-234-456-789
- email@resumeworded.com
- linkedin.com/in/username
- github.com/resumeworded

SKILLS	
Customer Relationship	
Management::	

• Eden Sales Manager (Advanced)

• Salesforce software

(Experienced)

- Oracle Eloqua
- HEAT Software Goldmine

Techniques:

- Account Management
- Project Management
- International Sales

Tools:●

MicroStrategy

- Microsoft Azure
- Airtable
- QlikTech QlikView
- IBM Cognos Impromptu

EDUCATION

Resume Worded University

Bachelor of Sales Management

Major in Regional Sales Management

Minors in International Trade

Awards: Resume Worded Teaching

Fellow (only 5 awarded to class), Dean's

List 2009 (Top 10%)

OTHER

 Volunteered in a 3-month sales techniques development project, run by ACB Corporation Inc.)

- ABC Certification (2022)
- Completed the Salesmastery

seminar course.